amplify.pt 2019-06-16

# Amplify Creations » Amplify Creations Privacy Policy

### Amplify Creations Privacy Policy

Please note that we may revise this privacy policy at any time. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on our websites. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. This privacy policy was last updated on May 14th, 2018.

By using our website you consent to Amplify Creations use of Cookies for operational or analytic/tracking use. The tracking information allows us to better understand the kind of users who visit our site and what content they’re interested in, or even their general geographical location. If you do not agree with the use of cookies please close our website and remove any created cookie data using your browser settings. Web analytics data and cookies cannot be used to identify you – they do not contain personal information such as your name or email address.

#### Contact Information

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at: **info@amplify.pt**

#### What are Cookies?

Cookies are small data files which save and retrieve information about your visit to a website or application. They reside in your Internet browser to help remember your preferences and previous activity. For example, cookies can help an online store remember the items you’ve put into your shopping cart, or advertisers can use cookies to target ads that are most relevant to you. You can find more information about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

**To our knowledge, when you visit our website, the following categories of cookies may be set in your browser:**

**Google Analytics:** Web analytics services to recognize your browser or device and, for example, identify whether you have visited our website before, what you have previously viewed or clicked on, and how you found us. The information is anonymous and only used for statistical purposes, and it helps us to analyse patterns of user activity and to develop a better user experience. No personally identifying data is included in this type of tracking, all of our activity falls within the bounds of the [Google Analytics Terms of Service](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html). You can opt-out from Google Analytics related services here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

**Firewall and Abuse Prevention:** We use a “Live Traffic” cookie to determine if someone is a human or bot, and to identify repeat visitors and display this in the Admin Live Traffic feed; a Country Blocking cookie so we can choose to use a cookie to bypass Country Blocking; and a Session cookie to remember if someone is a logged in user.

**Community Forum:** Forum platform for registered users, uses standard operational session cookies.

#### Scope

**Personal Information**  
This privacy policy applies to Amplify Creations customers, visitors, forum users, download system users, and newsletter subscribers. In accordance with [EU General Data Protection Regulation](https://www.eugdpr.org/), Amplify Creations does not directly collect any personal identifying information without user consent, or any type of anonymous visitor information. Amplify Creations will not, under any circumstances, unless legally obliged to, share any type of user information with external parties.

**Visitors**

  * No data collected by Amplify Creations, Google Analytics and Firewall and Abuse Prevention cookies/tracking used when applicable.

  * Incorrect usage or abuse will trigger an IP log that ensures that the address is blocked, thus preventing any damage to our website and our users.
  * Unity Asset Store users can access our products by inputting their Asset Store product invoice number. Invoice processing is entirely done by [Unity Technologies](https://unity3d.com/company), we do not access any identifying user information, nor is it shared by the available Unity store API, only the status of the access for any given product in order to offer a private download link to our customers. For additional information on how Unity handles your data, please check their [Privacy Policy](https://unity3d.com/legal/privacy-policy).

  * Forum registration requires a user supplied Username, Password, and Email Address. Data is securely stored and abides by EU GDPR requirements and used solely for operational purposes.

  * Newsletter registration requires a user supplied email. Data is adequately stored, abides by EU GDPR requirements, used solely for direct user marketing. Users may opt-out at any time by using the unsubscribe link present in all newsletter emails, or simply by contacting us directly.

  * Product Wiki registration requires a user supplied Username, Password, and Email Address; there’s also an optional “Real Name” section. Data is securely stored and abides by EU GDPR requirements and used solely for operational purposes.

#### Safeguards

Please note that no system can be guaranteed to be completely secure. While we strive to employ adequate protections for your data that are appropriate to its sensitivity, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of the information you share with us and we cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, loss or inadvertent disclosure of your information. In case of a breach, our servers will be immediately locked, we’ll determine if any data has been accessed and inform all the affected users.

#### Third-party websites

This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of third-party websites linked in our own. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them.

#### Third-party Web Frameworks and Services

We do not accept any responsibility or liability for any third-party policy changes that, without our knowledge, introduce unwanted cookies tracking.
